seojobs.in 2015-12-29

# Privacy Policy | SEO Jobs

This is the Privacy Policy for [SEOjobs.in](http://www.seojobs.in/)

If you have any further queries or If you need any more information about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us. We can be reached here: jobs @ seojobs.in

At SEOjobs.in, the privacy of our website visitors is very important to us. Therefore,  we have developed a Privacy Policy to address your concerns & explain certain choices you can make about the manner in which your information is collected and used on SEOjobs.in.

The information we collect on SEOjobs.in.

On SEOjobs.in , we display seo & internet marketing job offers. For potential candidates to get in touch with your company, you shall need to provide your contact details. This is information is Voluntarily provided by you for your benefit. No personal information is collected from visitors to SEOjobs.in unless you provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly.

The website traffic analyzer may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit SEOjobs.in, by using cookies. This does not personally identify you or extract any information from your PC or laptop computer or mobile. Website traffic analysers are used to provide to measure and monitor the use of SEOjobs.in and to improve the usability & design of the website and its content.  Information collected by traffic analysers include:  the date and times when SEOjobs.in is accessed, the url of the website from which people are referred to SEOjobs.in, country, state & city. Any info or data that would personally identify you as an individual entity is known only when you have voluntarily submitted it yourself.

At [SEOjobs.in](http://seojobs.in/) we have several advt partners to bring you the best offers. We have relationships with companies like Google through their Adsense program (www.google.com/adsense) for providing advertisements on SEOjobs.in. In the future, we may have partnerships with additional such advertising companies. For more information about this, you may consult the privacy policies of Google here http://www.google.com/privacy.html. These ad serving companies may collect information like your IP address through cookies. We have no access to this information at all.

For any further information, get in touch with us here jobs @ seojobs.in
